Done! Congratulations on your new bot. You will find it at t.me/BimkomiBot. You can now add a description, about section and profile picture for your bot, see /help for a list of commands. By the way, when you've finished creating your cool bot, ping our Bot Support if you want a better username for it. Just make sure the bot is fully operational before you do this.

Use this token to access the HTTP API:
7722019620:AAEYueraVyfFRFQMuY5DBFlNJcVpIwD_iPM
Keep your token secure and store it safely, it can be used by anyone to control your bot.

For a description of the Bot API, see this page: https://core.telegram.org/bots/api

BimkomiMain.py

def start(update: Update, context: CallbackContext) -> None:
    welcome_message = (
        "במקומי תשלח הודעה אוטומטית להזכיר לחבר להחזיר לך מה שהשאלת לו, במקומך. "
        "אל תרגיש יותר לא נעים להזכיר!"
    )
    update.message.reply_text(welcome_message)

# Token שקיבלת מ-BotFather
BOT_TOKEN = "YOUR_BOT_TOKEN_HERE"